He was dead... but he got better.
Crank: High Voltage is a action, thriller, crime
film directed by Mark Neveldine.
Chelios faces a Chinese mobster who has stolen his nearly indestructible heart and replaced it with a
battery-powered ticker that requires regular jolts of electricity to keep working.
Chev Chelios, played by Jason Statham.
Eve, played by Amy Smart.
Poon Dong, played by David Carradine.
Doc Miles, played by Dwight Yoakam.
Ria, played by Bai Ling.
El Huron, played by Clifton Collins Jr..
Crank: High Voltage (alternately titled Crank 2: High Voltage) is a 2009 American action film directed by Neveldine/Taylor, and
stars Jason Statham, Amy Smart, Clifton Collins Jr., Efren Ramirez, Bai Ling, David Carradine and Dwight Yoakam.
It is the sequel to the 2006 film Crank and also features several cameo
appearances of celebrities from various fields of entertainment.
In the film, Chev Chelios (Statham) survives from the deadly fall and gets kidnapped by Chinese doctors, who harvest
his heart and replace it with an artificial one, which is designed to keep him alive for an hour.
Chev sets out to find his heart while keeping himself
electrically charged to stay alive.
Crank: High Voltage was released in the United Kingdom on April 15, 2009
and was later released in North America on April 17, 2009.
Critics were not given advance screening of the film.
The film received praise for Statham's performance, but the film was criticised
for being excessively violent, offensive and visually unappealing.
The film explores themes of prostitute, heart,
horse race, cigarette, electric shock.
The tone is intense.